这蛋糕太好吃了
This cake is amazing!
天啊
My God,
开房去吧
get a room.
开房好啊
I would get a room with this cake.
我一定会让这蛋糕好好爽爽
I think I could show this cake a good time.
如果你必须放弃一样的话
If you had to,
你会放弃哪一样儿
what would you give up,
食物还是性爱
food or sex?
性爱
Sex.
说真的
Seriously,
你回答得也太快了吧
answer faster.
对不起  亲爱的
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
她刚才说的性爱
But when she said "sex,"
我没想到是指和你一起的性爱
I wasn't thinking about sex with you.
好象我还受了很大恩惠似的
It's like a giant hug.
罗斯  你呢
Ross, how about you?
你会放弃哪一样  性爱还是食物
Which would you give up?
食物
Food.
那如果是性爱和恐龙呢
How about sex or dinosaurs?
老天啊
Oh, my God,
这简直就像《苏菲的选择》
it's like Sophie's Choice.
哦  天啊
Oh, God.
乔伊  你放弃什么
What about you, Joe?
性爱还是食物
What would you give up, sex or food?
我不知道  这太难取舍了
I don't know, it's too hard.
不行  你必须得选一个
No, you gotta pick one.
食物  不  性爱
Food. No, sex.
食物  性爱  食物  性爱…
Food. Sex. Food. Sex--
我不知道  老天  我都想要
I don't know! Oh, God, I want both!
我要坐在面包上的妞儿
I want-- I want girls on bread!
你看看艾玛这些新照片
You gotta see these pictures of Emma.
哇  真可爱啊
Oh, how cute!
她看上去就象个洋娃娃
She looks just like a little doll.
不不  那就是个洋娃娃
Oh, no, that is a doll.
噢  感谢上帝
Oh, thank God,
因为我觉得它看上去有点吓人
because that thing's really creepy.
钱德勒在那儿
Look, there's Chandler.
噢  那个金发女郎是谁
Who's the blond?
她很漂亮
She's pretty.
他有外遇了
He's having an affair.
他才不是有外遇呢
He is not having an affair!
你知道的啦  我在这事儿上面感觉很准的
I'm always right about these things.
不  你才没有呢
No, you're not.
上周你还在想罗斯想把你宰了
Last week, you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
对不起
Well, sorry,
但确实很让人难以相信
but it's hard to believe
如果不是真的
that anyone would tell a story that dull...
谁会讲那么无聊的事
...just to tell it.
我敢发誓他们俩之间肯定有些什么事
There's something going on with them.
快看  他们俩上了同一部车
Look! He's getting into the car with her.
那并不能说明什么
That doesn't mean anything.
是吗  让我们走着瞧
Oh, yeah? Well, let's see.
喂  趴低点
Okay, duck down.
-喂  -嗨  钱德勒  我是菲比
- Hello? - Hi, Chandler. It's Phoebe.
我知道今天莫尼卡要上班
I know that Monica is working today...
所以我想你要不要
...so I was wondering if you wanted to
跟我和瑞秋一起去看电影
come to the movies with me and Rachel.
噢  我也得上班
Oh, I have to work too.
我这一天在办公室也走不开
Yeah, I'm stuck here at the office all day.
太可惜了  你不能去看电影
Well, it's a shame that you'll miss the movie...
因为我们打算看
...because we were gonna see, you know,
《骗子  骗子》
either Liar Liar...
《出卖我的爱》或者是《不了情》
...or Betrayal or An Affair to Remember.
这些片子都够老啊
Those are all really old.
是啊  也可能会看
Okay, then maybe it'll be--
《老兄  我的车呢》
Dude, Where's My Car?
-什么  -他们现在在车里
- What? - They're in a car.
好了  迟点再跟你说  再见
Okay. Well, talk to you later, okay? Bye.
快
Okay, quick.
我们得拦辆出租车跟踪他们
We gotta find a cab and follow them.
好的
Yeah, okay.
我得先去拿我的夜视镜和眩晕枪
Let me just grab my night-vision goggles and my stun gun.
我这儿有
I got them.
-嘿  -嗨  亲爱的
- Hey. - Hey. Hi, sweetie.
你身上有香水和烟的味道
Hey, you smell like perfume and cigarettes.
我今天和南茜在车里面呆了一天
I was in the car with Nancy.
南茜可不抽烟
Nancy doesn't smoke.
香水不是我的
Well, at least the perfume's not mine.
你就应该谢天谢地了
Be thankful for that.
那么  你认为那房子怎么样
So.... What did you think of the house?
简直太棒了  就是我们一直以来要找的
It's everything we've been looking for.
是吗  那些漂亮的方木涂层
Isn't it? And what about the amazing wanes coating...
拱形屋顶以及阁楼上的天窗
...the crown molding and the dormer windows in the attic?
还有蠕虫和爬虫
And the wiggle woms and the zip zorps!
你刚刚在说什么
What were the things you said?
你喜欢那个大院子吗
Don't you love the huge yard?
还有睡房里的壁炉
The fireplace in the bedroom.
南茜还说这个价钱非常优惠
And Nancy said it's really underpriced...
因为那家伙丢了工作
...because the guy lost his job
不得不搬去跟父母住  所以急于出手
and has to move in with his parents!
看把你兴奋的
This is bringing out a lovely color in you.
你认为我们是不是应该把它买下来
So do you think we should get it?
我不知道  你怎么想
I don't know. What do you think?
我想我们应该买下来
I think we should.
我也这么想
I do too.
这是很大件事
This is huge.
你有多想抽烟
How bad do you wanna smoke right now?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you mean,
大只会说话的香烟
giant, talking cigarette.
对了  我正在南茜车上的时候
Phoebe called as I was getting
菲比打电话来了
into Nancy's car.
如果她问起就说我一天都在工作
If she asks you, I was at work all day.
明白  你打算什么时候跟他们说这件事
Got you. When do we tell them?
先不告诉  没有十成的把握
We don't. Not until it's 100 percent.
干嘛弄得大家都难受
Why upset everybody over nothing?
嗯  好的
Okay. Right.
天啊  这将非常难以开口
Oh, my God, that is gonna be so hard.
我知道  所以祝你顺利吧
I know. Good luck with it.
我就是不明白钱德勒为什么搞外遇
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
告诉你们吧  我们一直跟踪他们
I'm telling you guys, we followed them
到一所位于韦斯特切斯特的房子的外面
out to a house in Westchester.
他们在里面待了有45分钟
They went in for 45 minutes,
出来的时候两人看上去都很高兴
and then they came out looking pretty happy.
钱德勒
Chandler?
45分钟
Forty-five minutes?
肯定有什么地方不对
Well, something's not right.
我不敢相信他这样对莫尼卡
I can't believe he'd do this to Monica.
是啊  而且他们就快有小孩儿了
I know, and with the baby coming?
那我们该不该告诉莫尼卡
So should we tell her?
我不知道
I don't know.
菲比  如果我们看到迈克跟另一个女人在一起
Phoebe, if one of us saw Mike with another woman,
我们应不应该告诉你
would you want us to tell you?
什么  你看到他跟谁在一起了
Why? Who'd you see him with?
没有  我只是说
No one. I'm just saying if we did--
告诉我你知道些什么
Tell me what you know!
没谁  没有
No one! Nothing!
迈克是个好人  我只是在假设
Mike's a great guy! It was hypothetical!
好了  他是个好人
All right. He is a good guy.
你是对的  他不会搞外遇
You're right. He wouldn't cheat.
如果我真看到他跟另一个女人在一起
If I did see him with someone,
我也绝不会
there's no way l--
你看见他跟谁在一起了
Who did you see him with?
看看她  多开心啊
Oh, look at her. So happy.
要是有更小的
If only there were a smaller one
来清理这个该有多好
to clean this one.
钱德勒在吗
Hey, is Chandler here?
不在  他去买饭了
No, he's picking up dinner.
怎么了  出什么事了吗
Why? What's up?
无论发生什么事
Look, whatever happens,
我们都跟你在一起  我们爱你
we're here for you, and we love you.
好
All right.
我想钱德勒可能有外遇了
Chandler might be having an affair.
什么
What?
菲比和我今天
Phoebe and I saw Chandler...
在街上
...with a blond woman today
看见钱德勒和一个金发女郎在一起
outside on the street.
然后我们跟踪他们到了
And then we followed them
一所位于韦斯特切斯特的房子
to a house in Westchester.
他们一起进去了
They went in together.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我的天啊  这太糟糕了
Oh, my God, that's awful.
你们觉得那房子怎么样
What did you think of the house?
什么
What?
莫尼卡  你明白
Monica, you understand
我们刚才说的话  对不对
what we're saying, right?
明白  当然明白
Yeah. Sure.
明显对我是毁灭性的打击
I mean, I'm devastated, obviously.
你们觉得那附近住人舒服不
Did you think the neighborhood was homey?
嘿
Hey.
你这个狗杂种
You son of a bitch.
只是我自己这么觉得
Is it me,
还是我们打招呼的用语
or have the greetings
真的在走下坡路
gone downhill around here?
菲比和瑞秋今天看见
Phoebe and Rachel saw you
你和南茜在一起
with Nancy today.
他们以为你和她有一腿
They think you're having an affair.
谁是南茜
Who's Nancy?
到底是怎么回事
What's going on?
好的
Okay....
好的  好的  伙计们  坐下说话
All right, you better sit down.
这是件大事
This is-- This is pretty big.
是的
Yeah.
我没有外遇
I'm not having an affair.
南茜是我们的房地产经纪
Nancy is our realtor.
我就知道他不可能
I knew he couldn't be with a woman
跟一个女人做45分钟那么长
for 45 minutes!
你们为什么要请地产经纪
Why do you have a realtor?
最近以来她带着我们
She's been showing us houses
去看郊区的房子
outside of the city.
什么
What?
你是说真的
Are you serious?
当我们发现我们
When we found out
马上就要有小孩儿了
that we were gonna get this baby...
我和钱德勒商量过了
...Chandler and I decided
我们决定不能在市区抚养我们的小孩儿
we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.
所以你们要搬出去
So you're-- So you're gonna move?
我的天
Oh, my God.
这种事我们总要投票解决吧
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
在市区里带小孩儿有什么不妥吗
What is wrong with raising a kid in the city?
我就这样啊
I'm doing it.
罗斯也这样
Ross is doing it.
莎拉·杰西卡·派克也是这么干的
Sarah Jessica Parker is doing it!
对你们来说这没什么问题
And that's great for you guys,
但是我们想要给孩子一片草地和一个的秋千
but we want a lawn and a swing set.
还有一条小孩
A street where our kids
可以在上面骑单车的马路
can ride their bikes...
不时还会有雪糕车经过
...and maybe an ice-cream truck can go by.
所以你们想买一栋50年代的房子
So you want to buy a house in the '50s.
你们有没有想过
Have you thought about
你们正放弃什么
what you're giving up?
你们不能搬出市区  如果...
You can't move out of the city. What if--?
如果你们想凌晨五点钟吃中餐怎么办
What if you want Chinese food at 5 a.m.?
又或者想买一块
Or a fake Rolex
一下雨就散架的假劳力士怎么办
that breaks as soon as it rains?
又或者一个电话就能到的
Or an Asian hooker
亚洲应召女郎呢
sent right to your door?
知道吗
You know what?
如果你们只是想看看房子  没问题
If you want to look for a house, that's okay.
不  不  不  别听他的
No! No, it's not! Don't listen to him.
小心我扁你
I'm gonna thump you.
的确是没问题
It's okay,
因为他们必须得把想搬走的这心情发泄出来
because they have to get it out of their system.
你们会发现
Okay? But you're gonna realize
这里才是你们真正想要住的地方
this is the only place you want to be.
实际上...
Actually...
我们已经找到合我们心意的房子了
...we already found a house we love.
什么
What?
大约一小时以前
About an hour ago,
我们开出了我们的价码
we made an offer.
我想你们现在
Bet you wish I was having
宁可我有外遇了吧
an affair now, huh?
你们已经开出价码了
You put an offer on a house?
那房子真的很好
It's so sweet.
的确是
It really is.
那里有一个很大的院子
It has this big yard
一直通到一条小溪
that leads down to this stream.
那里还有很多老枫树
And then there's these old maple trees.
跟自然环境有什么关系
Oh, again with the nature.
你们又不是海狸
What are you, beavers?
我知道你们一时很难接受我们的决定
Look, I know this is really hard,
我们也非常的抱歉
and we're really sorry.
是不是因为我常不敲门
Is this because I come over here
就过来拿你们的东西吃?
without knocking and eat your food?
我可以不那样做
Because I can stop doing that.
我真的可以改
I really, really think I can.
乔伊  你知道这不是我们要搬出去住的原因
You know that's not the reason, Joe.
我想如果你们到实地看一看的话
I think if you saw it,
你们会明白的
you'd understand.
你们俩去看过
You guys were there.
那的确很美  不是吗
It's beautiful, isn't it?
是  确实是很美
Yeah, it is.
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
的确是  好吧
Well, it is, all right?
我们今天到那儿的时候
When we were out there today,
我所想的是
all I kept thinking was:
我简直不敢相信
"l can't believe Chandler's
钱德勒在和那女人干那事儿
screwing this woman...
但是住这地方也太好了
...but, man, this would be a nice place to live!"
是  但住这也很好啊
Yeah, but so is this.
对  我是说
Yeah. I mean,
如果你们搬到那里去住
if you move there,
你们就得离开这儿了
you have to leave here.
你们怎么能离开这个地方
I mean, how can you leave this place?
老爸  你听我说
Come on, Daddy, listen!
从生下来  人们就跟我说
All my life, everyone's always told me,
"你是一只鞋"
"You're a shoe!"
"你是一只鞋
"You're a shoe!
你是一只鞋
You're a shoe.
你是一只鞋"
You're a shoe!"
今天我停下来说
I stopped and said,
"如果我不想当只鞋子会怎样
"What if I don't want to be a shoe?
如果我想做一个钱包
What if I want to be a purse?
或是顶帽子"
Or a hat?"
不  我不是要你给我买顶帽子
I don't want you to buy me a hat, l--
我是说我是一顶…
I'm saying I am a ha-
我只是打个比方  老爸
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
你知道他的问题在哪里了
You can see where he'd have trouble.
好吧  也许我就跟莫尼卡住在这儿
Well, maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
我想我们已经就谁
I guess we've established
和莫尼卡住在一起这个问题达成了共识
she's staying with Monica.
你的钱马上归我啦  格林小姐
Your money's mine, Greene.
你的尿门没拉上  盖勒先生
Your fly's open, Geller.
伙计们  知道我刚发现了什么吗
You know what I just realized?
Joker是带"J"的Poker
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J"!
巧合吧
Coincidence?
嗯  那是带"C"的"joincidence"
That's "joincidence" with a "C"!
呃  看
Look!
那个奇丑的裸男点了一堆蜡烛
Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
那太疼了
That had to hurt!
嗨  这也是你们的感恩节
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving too.
除了看球赛
Instead of watching football,
你也可以过来帮我们干点活
you could help.
我们会的
We know.
瑞秋  你得把这些果酱软糖
Rachel, you want to put the marshmallows
摆成一个同心圆
in concentric circles.
不  莫尼卡
No, Mon.
是你想把它们摆成那样
You want to put them in concentric circles.
我只是想这样
I want to do this.
每年如是
Every year.
我被卡住了
It's stuck!
别着急  小心阶梯
Step.
你怎么会把头给套进去了
How did it get on?
我想把它戴上去吓吓钱德勒
I put it on to scare Chandler.
我的天
Oh, my God!
莫尼卡会被吓死的
Monica's going to totally freak out!
还有  这里面难闻得要命
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
那是当然了
Of course it smells bad.
你脑袋伸到火鸡的屁股里面去了
You have your head up a turkey's ass.
莫尼卡
Monica.
嗨  你们把火鸡...
Did you get the turkey--?
啊  我的天
Oh, my God!
这是谁
Who is that?
是乔伊
It's Joey.
有了
I got it!
如果我们赢
If we win,
你们就得把那公鸡拿走
they have to get rid of the rooster.
这主意好
That's interesting!
如果你们赢
If you win...
我们就放弃那只鸟儿
...we give up the bird.
但是如果我们赢了
But if we win...
我们要你们住的地方
...we get your apartment.
-一言为定  -什么
- Deal! - What?
莫妮卡在当曲棍球守门员时
"What was Monica's nickname
绰号是什么
when she was a hockey goalie?"
-大胖子守门员  -正确
- Big Fat Goalie. - Correct!
瑞秋说她最喜欢的电影是
"Rachel claims it's her favorite movie."
《孽恋焚情》
Dangerous Liaisons.
正确  实际上她最喜欢的电影是
Correct, "Her actual favorite movie is...?"
《老板渡假去》
Weekend at Bernie's.
莫妮卡给她的毛巾分类
"Monica categorizes her towels.
一共分了多少类
How many categories are there?"
-每天用的  -华丽的
- Everyday use. - Fancy.
-客人的  -华丽客用的
- Guest. - Fancy guest.
-还剩2秒  -11种
- Two seconds. - Eleven?
11种  太不可思议了  11种是正确答案
Eleven! Unbelievable! Eleven is correct.
钱德勒第一次
"Chandler was how old
摸女孩子胸部的时候有多大
when he first touched a girl's breast?"
-14岁  -  不  19岁
- 14? - No, 19.
谢了兄弟
Thanks, man.
乔伊有一个想象中的童年时的朋友
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
-他叫什么名字  -莫里斯
- His name was...?" - Maurice!
正确  他是干什么的
Correct! "His profession was...?"
太空牛仔
Space cowboy!
钱德勒·宾的工作是什么
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
还有10秒
Ten seconds.
你们得答对这一题  否则就输了
You need this or you lose.
嗯  好象是跟传送有关的
Something to do with transponding.
啊  啊  是搬运工
He's a transpons...transponster!
你说的都不是个单词
That's not even a word!
你们这些讨厌的家伙
You are mean boys
真是太讨厌啦
who are just being mean!
嗨  别冲我们发火
Don't get mad!
没人逼你越赌越大
No one forced you to raise the stakes.
不对  是她逼我的
That is not true! She forced me!
要不是你答错了题
Hey, we would still be living here
我们还住这呢
if you hadn't gotten the question wrong!
那是一个愚蠢的  不公平的问题
It was a stupid, unfair question!
不要把责任怪在题上
Don't blame the questions!
你们能不能不要在屋子里瞎嚷嚷
Stop yelling in our apartment!
你们把我们乔迁新居的日子给毁了
You are ruining moving day for us.
钱德勒
Chandler!
钱德勒  我从窗户那里瞧见你们在干那事儿了
I saw what you were doing in the window!
我看见你在对我妹子做什么
I saw what you're doing to my sister!
现在你给我滚出去
Get out here!
哇  听着  我们的爱情长跑很长了
Listen, we had a good run.
有多久  四个月  五个月
What was it? Four, five months?
我的意思是这已经超过
I mean that's more
大多数人一辈子的恩爱时光了
than most people have in a lifetime.
再见了  自己保重  再见
So, goodbye, take care, byebye.
嘿  罗斯
Hey, Ross.
出什么事了  老哥
What's up, bro?
你们到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
嘿  出什么事了
What's going on?
我想  我想罗斯知道我和莫尼卡的事
I think...I think Ross knows about me and Monica.
老兄  他在那呢
Dude, he's right there.
我还当你是我最好的朋友呢
I thought you were my best friend!
她可是我亲妹子
This is my sister!
我最好的朋友跟我妹子
My best friend and my sister!
我简直不敢相信
I cannot believe this!
我们不是玩玩而已的
We're not just messing around.
我爱她
I love her.
我跟她坠入情网了
I'm in love with her.
真不好意思
I'm so sorry
你是这样发现我们的恋情的
that you had to find out this way.
抱歉  但这是真的
I'm sorry, but it's true.
我也爱他
I love him too.
我最好的朋友和我妹妹
My best friend and my sister!
我简直不敢相信
I cannot believe this!
这是你最后一箱衣服
This is the last box of your clothes.
我会在上面贴个标签
I'm just gonna label it
写"你在想什么"
"What were you thinking?"
有趣  因为我正想到对门去
I was gonna go across the hall
在钱德勒身上也写上这句话
and write that on Chandler.
二位  我不想把事情搞砸
Guys, I don't mean to make things worse, but...
但是我不想跟瑞秋住在一起了
...l don't want to live with Rachel anymore.
-什么  -什么
-What? -What?
你们对对方太刻薄了
You're so mean to each other.
我也不想像现在这样  弄得跟瑞秋不欢而散
I don't wanna end up like that with Rachel.
我还是喜欢你
I still like you.
菲比  那没关系  因为我不搬了
That's fine because I'm not moving.
菲比  你得跟把她带走
Phoebe, you gotta take her.
你知道  我是曾说过一些她的坏话
You know, I know I said some bad stuff...
但是  瑞秋还是有很多优点的
...but Rachel has qualities
这足以让她成为一个好的室友
that make her a good roommate.
她有很多商品目录
She gets tons of catalogs and she folds
她会把那些她认为我会喜欢的产品所在页折起来
she folds down the pages of things she thinks I'd like.
还有呢
What else?
在我洗澡的时候
When I take a shower...
她会在镜子上给我留言
...she leaves me notes on the mirror.
是  我确实这么干
I do. I do do that.
很好
That's nice.
我喜欢在洗手间里有东西读
I like having things to read in the bathroom.
当我看完书在沙发上睡着的时候
When I fall asleep on the couch...
她会为我盖上毯子
...she covers me with a blanket.
你知道啦  我不想凉着你
Well, you know, I don't want you to be cold.
还有  当我告诉她
And when I told her
我要搬过去跟钱德勒一起住的时候
that I was gonna move in with Chandler...
她真的是很支持我
...she was really supportive.
你太好了
You were so great.
你把一件困难的事情变得轻松简单
You made it so easy.
但现在你却要走了
And now you have to leave.
而我得和男生住一起
And I have to live with a boy!
-她真的走了  -我知道
- She really left. - I know.
-谢谢  -没问题  室友
- Thank you. - No problem, roomie.
-我能问你一个问题吗  -当然
- Can I ask you a question? - Sure.
那只狗在那儿干什么
What the hell is that dog doing here?
我来说点祝酒词吧
A little toast here. Ding, ding!
我知道这并不是
I know this isn't exactly
你们所计划的感恩节
the kind of Thanksgiving you planned...
但对于我来说  这个节真的是太棒了
...but for me this has been really great.
知道吗  可能是因为这个节
You know, I think because
没有人离婚
it didn't involve divorce...
吐得一塌糊涂
...or projectile vomiting.
无论怎样  我只是在想
Anyway, I think if
如果你们去了韦尔县
you had gone to Vail...
如果你们和你们的家人在一起
...or if you had been with your family,
如果你"没有"
or if you didn't have...
梅毒什么的
...syphilis and stuff...
我们就不可能在一起  对不对
...we wouldn't be all together.
所以  我想我要说的是
So I guess what I'm trying to say is...
我很感激你们
...that I'm very thankful
因为你们的感恩节计划全砸了
that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
-太感人了  -谢啦
- That's so sweet! - Thank you.
为糟糕的圣诞节干杯
Here's to a lousy Christmas!
也为糟糕的新年
And a crappy New Year!
此言极是
Hear, hear!
你们不能搬
You can't move.
你们就是不能这样做
You just-- You just can't.
瑞秋说得对
Rachel's right.
你们俩是属于这里的
This is where you guys belong.
是啊  你们肯定不会想住到韦斯特切斯特
Yeah.You don't wanna live in Westchester.
感觉那是最糟糕的切斯特
That's the worst of the Chesters.
知道吗
You know,
有时我独自一人在我的寓所的时候
sometimes when I'm alone in my apartment,
望向这边
I look over here...
你们正在吃晚餐
...and you guys are just having dinner...
看电视或是做着其它什么事
...or watching TV or something...
这会让我感觉好很多
...but it makes me feel better.
你们搬走后  我再望过来的时候
And now when I look over,
我会看到谁
who am I gonna see?
张三  李四  王二麻子
The Gottliebs? The Yangs?
他们不会让我感觉如此之好
They don't make me feel so good.
是啊  所以别搬了
Yeah. So don't move, okay?
对  就留下吧
Just stay here...
晚上的时候别忘了拉窗帘就行了
...and maybe close your blinds at night.
喂
Hey.
Hello?
是南茜  他们答复我们开出的价码了
It's Nancy. They responded to our offer.
结果呢
And?
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
他们对我们的出价没兴趣
They passed.
他们一个子儿也不愿少
They said they won't go a penny under the asking price.
-我们负担不起那价格  -我知道
- We can't afford that. - I know.
好了  如你们所愿了
Well, there you go.
真抱歉
I'm really sorry, you guys.
我也很抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry too.
要是那个电话在我说出从窗户那边望过来之前
I'm even more sorry that phone call didn't come...
打来的话  就好了
...before I told you about looking through the window.
我们还是让你们俩单独待一会儿吧
Yeah. Well, we're gonna let you be alone.
你们没事吧
You gonna be okay?
我们没事的
Yeah, we'll be okay.
我爱你们
Love you guys.
刚才没有支持你们
You know, I'm really sorry
很抱歉
I wasn't more supportive before.
没关系
That's okay.
我们能理解
We understand.
对了  关于这个南茜
Yeah, and about this Nancy....
如果你没跟她上床的话  能不能让我上
If you're not sleeping with her, should l?
我知道外面还有很多房子  但是我...
I know there'll be other houses, but I just--
-我太爱这栋房子了  -  是啊
- I love that one so much. - Yeah.
所以得到这栋房子是天大的喜事
Well, it's a good thing we got it then.
-什么  -我们买到那房子了
- What? - We got the house.
噢  我的天
Oh, my God.
我只是不想当着他们的面告诉你
I didn't wanna tell you in front of them.
我的天啊  我们得到了  我们买到那栋房子了
Oh my god, we got it?! We got the house?!
我们买到那栋房子了
We're getting a house!
-对  我们买房了  -还有小孩
- We're getting a house. - And a baby.
我们长大了
We're growing up.
是啊
We sure are.
-谁去跟他们说呢  -不是我
- Who's gonna tell them? - Not it!
不是我  讨厌
Not it! Damn it!
瑞秋  这是给你的
Rachel, this is yours.
为什么送我们这些礼物
Why? What are these for?
过会你就知道了
You'll see.
好了  大家都请打开来看看吧
All right, everybody open them.
好漂亮啊
Wow, this is so beautiful!
这个正是我上次在商店里相中的那一款
These are the ones I was looking at in the store!
-我知道  -我喜欢这个
- I know. - Oh, I love this!
赛百味肉丸三明治
A meatball sub!
谢谢
Thanks!
说真的  到底怎么回事
Seriously, guys, what's going on?
为什么送我们这些礼物
What are these for?
我先前不知道该怎么跟你们说
Well, I didn't know how to tell you before...
-但是  我们买到那房子了  -各位好好享受吧
- ...but we got the house. - Enjoy!
他们刚才说什么
What did they say?